Hello Hello friends, today's scene has come again
and we will discuss here in this video, it is
next week, then
between Saturday and April, which
companies are going to give their results here,
here I am discussing almost all the big companies
whose real faces are there, so here we will
discuss when the results of these companies
come today, then we will definitely make videos on them here
and we will also discuss their results
thoroughly and if you like my
work then please do subscribe to my channel,
what kind of list you
give me a lot, you want to
bring such videos
[Music]
Ajay,
now we will start next week which is going to be shown
and on Monday 20th April,
its result is going to come here and
many people will keep an eye on its result here, all the
investors who have called it in the IT sector companies, this will be very important for them
every day,
Victim Shukar will tell what kind of results are going to come here in the IT sector,
voting,
typing, the biggest computer, Infosys, there
Their result is about to come I
made a video about what
is activated by Infosys, what is the X factor,
I made a video about that, you
can go and watch it by clicking on the i button here
or you can access it in this skin,
Infosys has also announced a bike here
and we will see the points,
what is going to be the buyback in Infosys here,
Vipul, here is a big
IT company and here we will see
what kind of results they get, on 6th April we will see
our most awaited result on 117th which
is the biggest bank and private bank HDFC
Bank, on that day we are going to
see the video of the bank from here, 600 planes are going to be
bought by ICICI Lombard
and on Sunday April the
result of Bhansali Engineering College is going to come,
so last week it is a very good result,
just what happens in this poster, we
will see that on Sunday, do come to my channel,
we will discuss 12283 results, all these judges and
hmm, we will do LIC and see
what kind of results they get.  And the most
important thing is that
what kind of guidance will their president who will come for the next year,
it will be very important for all
this IT company, I hope you liked this small
video, if you
liked the video then definitely subscribe to the channel,
your father-in-law
requests me a lot to make videos,
we have trouble in this video, why poison